Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Administration Records 1853-2002 (bulk, 1929-1995) MS 3009-RG 5
New-York Historical Society
- Series VI. Executive Vice President Kelso Sutton Files, 1968-1994; 53 Linear feet in 53 record cartons
  - Subseries VI.B. Books Group Files, 1983-1993; 22.6 Linear feet in 24 record cartons
    - Book-of-the-Month Club: Kresch studies, 1992 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 1)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club: Offsite, 1992 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 2)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club: Strategic plan, 1992 April (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 3)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club: Strategic plan 1990-1994, 1989 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 4)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club: Strategic plan 1992, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 5)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club: Strategic plan update 1987-1991, circa 1986 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 6)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club: Strategic plan update 1988-1990, 1987 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 7)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club: Strategy meeting, 1989 April 28 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 8)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club: Miscellaneous, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 9-10)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club Week, 1988 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 11)
    - Books for Children, 1989 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 12)
    - Books for Children [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 19)
    - Books Group: General, 1986 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 13)
    - Books Group: Annual divisional incentive plan [RESTRICTED], 1986 August 5 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 17)
    - Books Group: Bonus list [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 18)
    - Books Group: Feasibility analysis, 1988 June 21 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 14)
    - Books Group: Joint Venture Committee, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 15)
    - Books Group: Management development issues, 1989 August 19 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 16)
    - Books Group: Operating review, 1987 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 17)
    - Books Group: Strategic plan, 1987 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 18-19)
    - Books Group: Strategic plan 1988-1990, 1987 October-1989 October 29 (Offsite-box 3787, Folder 20-21)
    - Books Group: Strategic plan update, 1992 (Offsite-box 3788, Folder 1)
    - Books Group International, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 3788, Folder 2)
    - Books Strategy Group meeting, 1988 October (Offsite-box 3788, Folder 3-5)
      1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Note on container: "Books Group Bermuda Hypermedia. October 1988." On label: "Times [sic] Inc. Meeting. Oct. 12 1988. Tape #1. Side 1."
    - Brack, Reginald: Books Group strategic plan 1985-1990, circa 1984 (Offsite-box 3788, Folder 6)
    - Brack, Reginald: Briefing, 1990 (Offsite-box 3788, Folder 7-8)
    - Brack, Reginald: McKinsey and Company study, 1983 January 31-May 26 (Offsite-box 3788, Folder 9-14)
    - Brack, Reginald: McKinsey and Company study, 1983 May 26-1985 July 23 (Offsite-box 3789, Folder 1-4)
    - Brack, Reginald: Time-Life Books executive summary 1984 budget/1985 forecast, 1983 November 13 (Offsite-box 3789, Folder 5)
    - Brack, Reginald: Yankelovich, Skelly and White study of corporate identity and reputation, 1984 March (Offsite-box 3789, Folder 6)
    - Budget: 1989 marketing budget, 1988 September 9 (Offsite-box 3789, Folder 7)
    - Budget: Book-of-the-Month Club 1990 budget, 1989 (Offsite-box 3789, Folder 8)
    - Budget: Book-of-the-Month Club 1991 budget, 1990 October 29 (Offsite-box 3789, Folder 9-10)
    - Budget: Books Group 1987 budget, 1986 November 3 (Offsite-box 3789, Folder 11)
    - Budget: Books Group 1988 budget, 1987 October 26-1988 October 24 (Offsite-box 3789, Folder 12-13)
    - Budget: Books Group 1989 budget (revised), 1988 February 26 (Offsite-box 3789, Folder 14)
    - Budget: Books Group 1988 budget reaction, 1987 (Offsite-box 3790, Folder 1)
    - Budget: Books Group 1989 budget (revised), 1988 December 9-11 (Offsite-box 3790, Folder 2)
    - Budget: Books Group 1989 budget review, 1988 (Offsite-box 3790, Folder 3-4)
    - Budget: Books Group 1990 budget review, 1989 (Offsite-box 3790, Folder 5)
    - Budget: Books Group 1991 budget background, 1990 (Offsite-box 3790, Folder 6)
    - Budget: Time Inc. Book Company 1990 year-end financial summary, 1991 (Offsite-box 3790, Folder 7)
    - Budget: Time Inc. Book Company 1991 budget, 1990 November 16 (Offsite-box 3790, Folder 8)
    - Budget: Time Inc. Books 1991 budget review, 1990 December 6 (Offsite-box 3790, Folder 9)
    - Budget: Time-Life 1991 budget, 1990 October 16-30 (Offsite-box 3790, Folder 10)
    - Budget: Time-Life Books worldwide operations detailed budget book, 1986 November 1 (Offsite-box 3790, Folder 11)
    - Budget: Time Warner Book Company 1990 budget presentation, 1989 November 27 (Offsite-box 3790, Folder 12)
    - Budget: Time Warner Libraries 1992 budget, 1991 October 17 (Offsite-box 3790, Folder 13)
    - Budget: Time Warner Publishing budget, 1992 (Offsite-box 3790, Folder 14)
    - Budget: Warner Publishing Inc. and subsidiaries budget, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 3790, Folder 15-17)
    - Budget: Warner Publishing Inc. and subsidiaries budget, 1992 (Offsite-box 3791, Folder 1)
    - Canada, 1986-1992 (Offsite-box 3791, Folder 2-3)
    - Century Hutchinson Limited, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 3791, Folder 4-6)
    - China, 1993 (Offsite-box 3791, Folder 7)
    - China project, 1992 (Offsite-box 3791, Folder 8)
    - Christian Verlag, 1987 (Offsite-box 3791, Folder 9)
    - Cloverdale Press, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 3791, Folder 10)
    - Co-location, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 3791, Folder 11)
    - Competitor prices, 1991 (Offsite-box 3791, Folder 12)
    - Conboy, Brian memoranda, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 3791, Folder 13)
    - Connections: American Business and the Mob book, 1990 (Offsite-box 3791, Folder 14)
    - Connections: American Business and the Mob book [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 20)
    - Cope Vyse Warwick, 1992 (Offsite-box 3791, Folder 15-17)
      1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on tape: "Cope Vyse Warwick. VO for CBOMC TV."
    - Copyright protection of database, 1992 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 1)
    - Corporate database project, 1986-1991 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 2)
    - Corporate Policy Committee, 1992 October 7-8 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 3)
    - Corporate Policy Committee Homestead Inn meeting, 1993 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 4)
    - Data center, 1992 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 5)
    - David and Charles, 1990 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 6-7)
    - DC Comics, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 8)
    - DialAmerica, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 9)
    - Distribution, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 10)
    - Doubleday Books, 1993 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 11)
    - Duncan, David Douglas, 1992 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 12)
    - Employee opinion survey, 1987 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 13)
    - Employee stock ownership plan (ESOP), 1987 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 14)
    - Esselte Publishing, 1990 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 15)
    - European privacy issue, 1991 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 16)
    - Expansion Publishing Group, 1993 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 17)
    - Expansion Publishing Group [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 21)
    - Favreul, Bertrand, 1990 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 18)
    - Field Publications, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 19-20)
    - Field Publications [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 22)
    - Franklin Library, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 3792, Folder 21)
    - Freedom Forum Media Studies Center, 1993 (Offsite-box 3793, Folder 1)
    - Fulfillment Task Force, 1990 December 19 (Offsite-box 3793, Folder 2)
    - Gorbachev, Mikhail fast book, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 3793, Folder 3)
    - Grand Livre du Mois book club, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 3793, Folder 4-5)
    - Grand Livre du Mois book club [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 23)
    - Groupe de la Cité, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 3793, Folder 6)
    - Gruppo DeAgostini, 1992 (Offsite-box 3793, Folder 7-8)
    - Hachette Distribution case, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 3793, Folder 9)
    - Hankook-Ilbo, 1991 (Offsite-box 3793, Folder 10)
    - History Book Club, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 3793, Folder 11-13)
    - History Book Club [RESTRICTED], 1987-1988 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 24)
    - Hodder and Stoughton, 1990 (Offsite-box 3793, Folder 14)
    - India, 1991 (Offsite-box 3793, Folder 15)
    - International: Asia, 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 3793, Folder 16)
    - International: Asia materials, 1991 (Offsite-box 3793, Folder 17)
    - International: Asia materials, 1991 (Offsite-box 3794, Folder 1)
    - International: Financial statistics on international publications, 1990 (Offsite-box 3794, Folder 2-3)
    - International Postal Forum, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 3794, Folder 4-7)
    - International Task Force: General, 1991 (Offsite-box 3794, Folder 8-11)
    - International Task Force: General [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 25)
    - International Task Force: Background materials, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 3794, Folder 12)
    - International Task Force: Background materials, 1991 (Offsite-box 3795, Folder 1)
    - International Task Force: International strategic plan update, 1991 April 3-June 26 (Offsite-box 3795, Folder 2-3)
    - International Task Force: International strategic planning sessions complete final meeting notes, 1991 May (Offsite-box 3795, Folder 4)
    - International Task Force: Interviews, 1991 (Offsite-box 3795, Folder 5)
    - Issue papers, circa 1988 (Offsite-box 3795, Folder 6)
    - KGB (Komitet Gosudarstvennoy Bezopasnosti), 1992 (Offsite-box 3795, Folder 7)
    - Little, Brown and Company: General, 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 3795, Folder 8-13)
    - Little, Brown and Company: General [RESTRICTED], 1990-1991 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 26)
    - Little, Brown and Company: Canada, 1989 (Offsite-box 3795, Folder 14)
    - Little, Brown and Company: Operations review, 1988 April 19 (Offsite-box 3795, Folder 15)
    - Little, Brown and Company: Professional division, 1989 (Offsite-box 3795, Folder 16)
    - Little, Brown and Company: Requests to buy, 1988-1991 (Offsite-box 3795, Folder 17)
    - Little, Brown and Company: Strategic plan update 1986-1991, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3795, Folder 18)
    - Little, Brown and Company: Strategic plan update, 1987 (Offsite-box 3795, Folder 19)
    - Little, Brown and Company: Strategic plan update (binder cover), 1987 (Offsite-box 3807, Folder 1)
    - Macdonald and Company, 1992 (Offsite-box 3795, Folder 20)
    - Madonna book, 1992 (Offsite-box 3795, Folder 21)
    - Magazine Group: Publishers' conference, 1988 (Offsite-box 3796, Folder 1)
    - Maildex, 1991 (Offsite-box 3796, Folder 2)
    - Maildex [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 27)
    - Management development [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 28)
    - Marakon Associates: Juvenile publishing, 1987 (Offsite-box 3796, Folder 3)
    - McKinsey and Company, 1987-1990 (Offsite-box 3796, Folder 4)
    - McKinsey and Company study, 1986 December 19-1987 October 19 (Offsite-box 3796, Folder 5-8)
    - Meetings, 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 3796, Folder 9)
    - Meetings, Montauk, 1990 July 30 (Offsite-box 3796, Folder 10)
    - Merger management, 1989 (Offsite-box 3796, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1984-1993 (Offsite-box 3796, Folder 12)
    - More than Just a Pretty Face book, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 3796, Folder 13)
    - MTV, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 3796, Folder 14-16)
    - Mysterious Press, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 3796, Folder 17)
    - Mysterious Press [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 29)
    - Nancy Hutches and Associates, 1989 (Offsite-box 3796, Folder 18)
    - New Systems Development, 1991 (Offsite-box 3796, Folder 19)
    - New York University, 1991 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 1)
    - News Corporation Limited, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 2)
    - Nicholas, Nick J., Jr., 1986-1989 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 3)
    - Oxmoor House, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 4)
    - Paramount, 1989 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 5)
    - Penguin Group, 1989 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 6)
    - Poets and Writers, 1992 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 7)
    - Pofcher Company, 1987-1992 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 8)
    - Pofcher Company [RESTRICTED], 1987-1988 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 30)
    - Political Action Committee, 1992 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 9)
    - Power Cooperation of Canada, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 10)
    - Price Stern Sloan, 1990 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 11)
    - Price Stern Sloan [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 31)
    - Privacy, 1991 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 12)
    - Project Orca, 1987 May 20 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 13)
    - Purchasing Committee policy, 1992 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 14)
    - Quality management review, 1991 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 15-16)
    - Quality Paperback Book Club, 1989 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 17)
    - Quill Corporation, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 18)
    - Quincy Jones project, 1990 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 19)
    - Reader's Digest, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 20)
    - Readers Garden, 1990 (Offsite-box 3797, Folder 21)
    - Recession information, 1987-1990 (Offsite-box 3798, Folder 1)
    - Record Club of Australia, 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 3798, Folder 2)
    - Recycling, 1992 (Offsite-box 3798, Folder 3)
    - Reed International Books, 1987-1988, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 3798, Folder 4-5)
    - Reed International Books [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 32)
    - Research activity report, 1993 (Offsite-box 3798, Folder 6)
    - Rushdie, Salman, 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 3798, Folder 7)
    - Russian book store, 1987 (Offsite-box 3798, Folder 8)
    - Sackler, Art, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 3798, Folder 9)
    - Schwarzkopf, Norman, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 3798, Folder 10)
    - Scott Foresman/Little Brown College Division: General, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 3798, Folder 11-12)
    - Scott Foresman/Little Brown College Division: Nursing, 1988 (Offsite-box 3798, Folder 13)
    - Scott Foresman/Little Brown College Division: Sale, 1988 (Offsite-box 3798, Folder 14)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: General, 1986-1989 (Offsite-box 3798, Folder 15-19)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: General, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 3799, Folder 1-3)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: General [RESTRICTED], 1986, 1990 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 33-34)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Announcements, 1986 (Offsite-box 3799, Folder 4)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Artandi, George as Chairman, 1988 (Offsite-box 3799, Folder 5)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Books Group binder, 1986 (Offsite-box 3799, Folder 6)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Canada Publishing Corporation, 1986 (Offsite-box 3799, Folder 7)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Escrow, 1992 (Offsite-box 3799, Folder 8)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Estimate/plan, 1987 September (Offsite-box 3799, Folder 9)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Financial, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 3799, Folder 10-11)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Financial miscellaneous, 1988 (Offsite-box 3799, Folder 12)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Final papers, 1990 (Offsite-box 3799, Folder 13-16)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Final papers [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Offsite-box R66, Folder 35)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Operating review, 1988 (Offsite-box 3799, Folder 17)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Personnel, 1986 (Offsite-box 3800, Folder 1)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Presentation to the Board of Directors, 1989 September 18 (Offsite-box 3800, Folder 2)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Presentation, 1989 October (Offsite-box 3800, Folder 3-4)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Profit plan 1987 and strategic plan 1988-1990, 1986 (Offsite-box 3800, Folder 5)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Project Scholar, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 3800, Folder 6-13)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Project Scholar [RESTRICTED], 1989 November (Offsite-box R66, Folder 36)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Purcell, Jack, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 3800, Folder 14)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Purchase agreement with Scott Acquisition Corporation [RESTRICTED], 1989 November (Offsite-box R66, Folder 37)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Real estate, 1985 (Offsite-box 3800, Folder 15)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Review, 1987 August (Offsite-box 3800, Folder 16)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Sale, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 3800, Folder 17)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Sale, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 3801, Folder 1-2)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Sale [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Offsite-box R67, Folder 1)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Sale award, 1989 December 29 (Offsite-box 3801, Folder 3)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Sale chronological notes, 1988 (Offsite-box 3801, Folder 4)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Sale notes, 1988 (Offsite-box 3801, Folder 5)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Severance [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Offsite-box R67, Folder 2)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Strategic plan, 1989? (Offsite-box 3801, Folder 6)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Strategic plan 1987-1990 (Offsite-box 3801, Folder 7)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Strategy, 1989 June (Offsite-box 3801, Folder 8)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Taxes, 1987 March (Offsite-box 3801, Folder 9)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Valuation background, 1986 (Offsite-box 3801, Folder 10)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Work papers, 1986 (Offsite-box 3801, Folder 11)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Work papers [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Offsite-box R67, Folder 3)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Miscellaneous, 1986 (Offsite-box 3801, Folder 12)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Offsite-box R67, Folder 4)
    - SFN Companies: Board of Directors material, 1988 (Offsite-box 3801, Folder 13)
    - SFN Companies: Documents, circa 1986 (Offsite-box 3801, Folder 14-15)
    - SFN Companies: College Textbook Initiatives (CTI), 1986 (Offsite-box 3801, Folder 16-17)
    - Softback preview, 1991 (Offsite-box 3801, Folder 18)
    - South Africa, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 3801, Folder 19)
    - Sports Illustrated for Kids, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 3802, Folder 1-2)
    - Staff memoranda binder, 1992 (Offsite-box 3802, Folder 3-4)
    - Technology: Systems upgrade plan, 1988 July 29 (Offsite-box 3802, Folder 5)
    - Time Inc.: International strategic plan, 1993 June (Offsite-box 3802, Folder 6)
    - Time Inc.: Marketing source book, 1993 (Offsite-box 3802, Folder 7-8)
    - Time Inc.: Strategic plan, 1992 October 5 (Offsite-box 3802, Folder 9)
    - Time Inc. Board of Directors: Meetings, 1991 (Offsite-box 3802, Folder 10)
    - Time Inc. Book Company: General, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 3802, Folder 11)
    - Time Inc. Book Company: Project sequel, 1992 February 10 (Offsite-box 3802, Folder 12)
    - Time Inc. Book Company: Project sequel (binder cover), 1992 February 10 (Offsite-box 3807, Folder 2)
    - Time Inc. Book Company: Project sequel follow-up questions, 1992 March 2 (Offsite-box 3802, Folder 13)
    - Time Inc. Book Division: AIP report, 1992 (Offsite-box 3802, Folder 14)
    - Time Inc. Book Division: Changes to AIP, 1993 (Offsite-box 3802, Folder 15)
    - Time Inc. Book Division: Strategic plan, 1992 (Offsite-box 3802, Folder 16-17)
    - Time Inc. Book Division: Strategic plan, 1992 (Offsite-box 3803, Folder 1)
    - Time Inc. Books: 1991 incentive awards, 1992 (Offsite-box 3803, Folder 2)
    - Time Inc. Books: Bank presentation, 1991 (Offsite-box 3803, Folder 3)
    - Time Inc. Books: Estimate, 1991 (Offsite-box 3803, Folder 4)
    - Time Inc. Books: Kleinwort Benson Limited presentation, Opportunities in European Media, 1991 July (Offsite-box 3803, Folder 5)
    - Time Inc. Books Direct, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 3803, Folder 6)
    - Time Inc. Books Direct strategy meeting, 1991 May 3 (Offsite-box 3803, Folder 7)
    - Time Inc. Books Group: Total compensation study, 1985 December 7 (Offsite-box 3803, Folder 8)
    - Time Inc. Magazine Company strategic plan, 1991 July (Offsite-box 3803, Folder 9)
    - Time Inc. Magazines strategic plan, 1991 February 7 (Offsite-box 3803, Folder 10)
    - Time Inc. Magazines strategic plan (binder cover), 1991 February 7 (Offsite-box 3807, Folder 3)
    - Time-Life strategic plan, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 3803, Folder 11-14)
    - Time-Life Books: General, 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 3804, Folder 1-3)
    - Time-Life Books: Background of move from New York, 1975, 1982 (Offsite-box 3804, Folder 4)
    - Time-Life Books: Condensed books, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 3804, Folder 5)
    - Time-Life Books: Controlled circulation magazine proposal, 1988 October 28 (Offsite-box 3804, Folder 6)
    - Time-Life Books: Digest proposal, 1989 June 31 (Offsite-box 3804, Folder 7)
    - Time-Life Books: "How We Make Books" manual, 1991 (Offsite-box 3804, Folder 8)
    - Time-Life Books: "How We Make Books" manual (binder cover), 1991 (Offsite-box 3807, Folder 4)
    - Time-Life Books: Organization, circa 1980s (Offsite-box 3804, Folder 9)
    - Time-Life Books: Special interest magazines proposal, 1989 January 17 (Offsite-box 3804, Folder 10)
    - Time-Life Books: Stolley, Richard, 1987-1991 (Offsite-box 3804, Folder 11)
    - Time-Life Books: Strategic plan, 1992 September 2 (Offsite-box 3804, Folder 12)
    - Time-Life Books: Strategic plan 1987-1991, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 3804, Folder 13-14)
    - Time-Life Books: Strategic plan 1988-1990, 1987 September 1 (Offsite-box 3804, Folder 15)
    - Time-Life Books: Strategy meeting, 1989 (Offsite-box 3804, Folder 16)
    - Time-Life Books International, 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 3804, Folder 17)
    - Time-Life Books International, 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 3805, Folder 1)
    - Time-Life Cable, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 3805, Folder 2)
    - Time-Life for Children: Children's publishing strategic plan 1988-1992, 1988 December 26 (Offsite-box 3805, Folder 3)
    - Time-Life Home Video: General, 1987-1991 (Offsite-box 3805, Folder 4-6)
    - Time-Life Home Video: Columbia, 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 3805, Folder 7)
    - Time-Life Home Video: Columbia [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Offsite-box R67, Folder 5)
    - Time-Life Libraries strategic plan 1989-1993, circa 1988 (Offsite-box 3805, Folder 8)
    - Time-Life Music, 1991 (Offsite-box 3805, Folder 9)
    - Time-Life Video, 1986-1991 (Offsite-box 3805, Folder 10)
    - Time-Life Video [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Offsite-box R67, Folder 6)
    - Time Warner bank meeting, 1989 June 29 (Offsite-box 3805, Folder 11)
    - Time Warner Direct, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 3805, Folder 12)
    - Time Warner Direct Entertainment, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 3805, Folder 13-14)
    - Time Warner Libraries, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 3805, Folder 15-17)
    - Time Warner Libraries status report, 1992 July 8 (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 1)
    - Time Warner Publishing: General, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 2)
    - Time Warner Publishing: Agenda for the '90s, ca. 1990 (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 3)
    - Time Warner Publishing: Kleinwort Benson Limited presentation, Preliminary Review of Strategic Options in Europe, 1992 February (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 4)
    - Time Warner Trade Publishing, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 5)
    - Time Warner Trade Publishing strategic plan, 1992 (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 6)
    - Troll Associates, 1988 (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 7-8)
    - Troll Associates confidentiality agreement [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Offsite-box R67, Folder 7)
    - Turner Publishing, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 9)
    - Video: AIDS: Everything you and your family needs to know... But were afraid to ask, 1987 October 14 (Offsite-box 3808, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (39 min., 3 sec): 1/2 in. On label: "T-60 10/14/87. 'AIDS. Everything you and your family needs to know... but were afraid to ask.' Part 1 of 1. TRT-39:03."
    - Video: HBO promotional facilities video tape, circa 1980s (Offsite-box 3808, Item 2)